Did you want to kill Jarvis?
I don't know what you mean.
I'll post the video online.
Let the Police find out what you
and your daughter did.
I already told you, it's YIO, not IOY.
Didn't you say Helen told you
YIO stands for a high school group
called Youth Investment Organization?
Why did it become IOY?
Wendy, what is it?
What are you doing here?
See for yourself.
I don't want anyone else to get hurt
from your pranks.
If you feel a shred of guilt
for paralyzing me...
I think you're quite mistaken.
I don't feel guilty at all.
Did you want to kill Jarvis?
I don't know what you mean.
Helen is your daughter.
No wonder you quit right after Jarvis died.
Even if he paralyzed your daughter,
there's no need to kill him.
Just because you found that video,
you can't accuse me of murder.
I really don't know what you mean.
You won't admit it? I'll post it online.
Let the Police find out what you
and your daughter did.
No!
(The truth about Ngai Ka-yan's death)
Cheong, there's a new post on J Weekly.
What? Ngai Ka-yan has just died.
I attended most of the
Alumni Association functions...
The truth about Ngai Ka-yan's death?
Who's that girl?
No!
Let go!
Give me the phone.
This place hasn't changed much.
The teachers who taught us are gone.
Let go!
I kicked a football tied to a fishing line.
I landed on my back and became paralyzed.
What happened? It stopped?
It was deleted!
Did you hear that?
The girl mentioned a football and
she was paralyzed.
That was obviously Lok Hiu-sin.
This video was uploaded using
the J Weekly account.
It's likely done by someone from
the online channel.
They want us to know there's more
to the case.
But why upload it and delete it right away?
None of these can last too long.
Luckily we ran into each other
and you told me you're going abroad
with your Mom for your treatment.
Or these would have gone to waste.
Take them all if you can use them.
Thank you.
Don't worry, if I can't use them
or have leftovers,
I'll take them to the food bank.
What's this? It's rattling inside.
That's Mom's stuff, not cup noodles.
She wants it. Please put it back.
Sorry, I'll put it back.
Auntie Ching, I just came from your house...
Hey...she blew me off!
Get in!
Yuen Kit-ching, you murderer! Open up!
What are you doing? Open the door...
Yuen Kit-ching, you murderer! Open the door!
Oh dear! She said she kept a copy.
That means she can show it again. I'm dead.
Mom, Mrs. Chan was just here...
Stop talking. Let's go to the airport now.
But we're leaving tomorrow night.
There's no time. We'll change our flight
at the airport.
We must leave tonight.
You haven't packed?
I'll help you pack.
Don't worry, everything uploaded
using our streaming platform
will have a copy on the server.
Only if I keep pulling pranks
on people without end,
will I be able to live up to the past
eight years you have been paralyzed.
Ngai Ka-yan is full of crap even after
he paralyzed someone.
He's a genuine scumbag.
Whoever uploaded this video
wants us to know
Lok Hiu-sin has a motive to
kill Ngai Ka-yan.
Let's bring her in.
Police! We're looking for Miss Lok Hiu-sin.
Helen? She's leaving soon.
Leaving? Where to?
Switzerland. Her flight was tomorrow.
But she just changed it to tonight.
Thanks.
The university just came out with
their duty roster.
Auntie Ching is on it.
Let's head out to the airport.
Thank you...
Sin, no matter what happens,
you must get on that plane.
What about you?
I'll join you later.
No!
Listen to me, you must leave.
Yuen Kit-ching, stay where you are!
Yuen Kit-ching, Lok Hiu-sin,
we suspect you're involved in
Ngai Ka-yan's murder.
We need you down at the station
to facilitate our investigation.
Sir, my daughter must leave.
I beg you to let us go.
You won't get away. Stop this.
Let me see her to the boarding gate.
Auntie Ching, stop.
Or you'll be resisting arrest.
You did everything for your daughter.
Don't make any more mistakes.
Mom...
Yuen Kit-ching, you're under arrest.
You're anxious to leave town,
is it because during the
Static Apnea Challenge,
you swapped Ngai Ka-yan's oxygen
cylinder into H2S?
You murdered him, that's why you
fled from justice?
I didn't kill anyone.
I'm not running away.
I'm taking my daughter to Switzerland
for treatment.
He paralyzed your daughter.
Don't you want revenge?
Whenever I think of my daughter's injury,
it really breaks my heart.
(Eight years ago)
Doctor, I'm Lok Hiu-sin's mother.
How is she?
Your daughter had an accident
while playing football
and injured her spinal nerves.
The worst scenario is
she may be paralyzed from the waist down.
We'll do our best.
Mom!
I'm sorry, I slipped while playing football
and ended up like this.
Well? How do you feel?
Does it hurt anywhere?
Not really. My legs can't feel anything.
Maybe the anesthetic hasn't worn off.
Oh dear, the try out for the
Hong Kong team is next week.
I wonder if I could get well in time.
What's wrong, Mom?
Nothing. I'm just worried.
I promise I'll be there for you.
You'll get well one day at a time.
I only found out eight years later,
it was Jarvis who paralyzed her.
Exactly! After you found out,
you were so angry you wanted to kill him.
Yes, I was angry.
But I would never kill him.
We checked the serial number
of the cylinder,
it matched the lot from the HKIU lab.
You worked there part-time
and quit right after the accident.
How do you explain that?
I have nothing to explain.
I haven't finished grade school.
I know nothing about chemistry.
My daughter is paralyzed,
and there's a new technology
that may help her walk again.
I quit my job so I can go with her
for the treatment.
What's wrong with that?
Lok Hiu-sin, we found out
Ngai Ka-yan paralyzed you.
Is that why you colluded with your Mom
to kill him?
It's true I have a beef with him.
But that doesn't mean I'll kill him.
I was injured the day of the livestreaming,
I was resting at home.
I found this pin in Ngai Ka-yan's office.
It bears the same logo as the pendant
on the bracelet
you wore when you recorded the TV show.
Did you drop it when you swapped the
cylinders in Ngai Ka-yan's office?
I was never at the channel office.
This pin is from a high school club.
What kind of club?
Youth Investment Organization.
The logo is the overlapping of Y, I and O.
They made several souvenirs.
Bracelets and pins.
Ngai Ka-yan and I both joined this club.
That's why we have souvenirs.
Thank you.
Lok Hiu-sin was right.
Youth Investment Organization does exist.
Lok Hiu-sin joined the sixth year,
Ngai Ka-yan was the fourth.
Maybe Ngai Ka-yan dropped the pin
and not the killer?
I went over all the statements.
No one at the channel has seen
Ngai Ka-yan wearing this pin.
It looked fairly new when I found it
in Ngai Ka-yan's office.
Must have happened recently.
Maybe someone picked up Ngai Ka-yan's pin
and dropped it without knowing it.
Most probably it's Auntie Ching.
She took her daughter's pin
and dropped it when she swapped
the cylinders.
Let's not rule out Auntie Ching acted alone
and Lok Hiu-sin knew nothing.
No, the mother brought the daughter
to go on the run.
The daughter is in the know.
But they won't admit anything.
Let them go.
What? We still have plenty of time.
We'll shake them up a bit longer.
Maybe they'll spill the beans.
We have no new evidence. Let her go.
Miss Lok, there are seats on a flight
tonight to Switzerland via London.
Will you consider it?
Give me time to think.
I see. Just a reminder,
the plane takes off in four hours.
If you decide to take it,
you'll need to leave for the airport now
to check-in.
Sin, no matter what happens,
you must get on that plane.
What about you?
I'll join you later.
No!
Listen to me, you must leave.
Brilliant, Gogo Sir!
Lok Hiu-sin came back here.
We have no new evidence. Let her go.
Just like that? What if they run away again?
Lok Hiu-sin is close to her mother.
She would not leave her behind.
If you were Lok Hiu-sin,
what would you do when you got out?
She'll do anything
to destroy incriminating evidence
against her mother.
Five cylinders were missing from
the university lab.
If they had them,
she'll find a way to dispose of them.
When she comes downstairs with the evidence,
we'll catch her red-handed.
Ko Sir, that guy looks familiar.
He's my ex-boyfriend.
We used to live together.
I was not well that day,
he came by to keep me company.
That's Lok Hiu-sin's boyfriend.
What's so urgent that you needed
me here right away?
What's wrong?
I shouldn't have asked you to come up.
But you're leaving next week.
There's no telling when you'll be back.
I want to see you one last time.
Silly. Don't say these things.
I'm not sure if I'll get another chance
to say this.
I really want you to know
I don't want to leave you.
Did something happen?
I prepared a present for you.
It's on the shelf in the kitchen.
Can you get it down?
Lok Hiu-sin summoned the dude
because she needs his help
to dispose of the cylinders.
Bingo...
You're giving me a case of cup noodles?
No, I needed your help getting that down.
Here's your present.
Open it when you get home.
Give it up.
I thought Ching could help stall you.
Your plan would have worked.
But your boyfriend unwrapped the
present early.
Cheong, stay on his tail.
Hello?
The bag only has a picture frame.
There were no cylinders inside.
You better tell us the whole story.
Madam, you're too kind to walk me
to my cell.
Shut up and get in.
Aren't we crowded today?
An auntie and a crippled girl.
What does she look like?
Is she in a wheelchair?
Yes. She looks young. Why? You know her?
We checked the serial number on the
cylinders you tried to toss.
They were highly concentrated H2S stolen
from the HKIU lab.
They were identical to the one Ngai Ka-yan
inhaled from.
How do you explain that?
The evidence we have indicates
you and your Mom Yuen Kit-ching
conspired to commit murder.
The act of disposing of the cylinders alone
can nail you for conspiracy
to commit murder.
It was entirely my own doing...
Yuen Kit-ching is willing to testify.
Sir, did you arrest my daughter?
Where is she now? Can I see her?
She's next door.
My colleague is questioning her.
I did it. She had nothing to do with this.
Don't press charges against her.
You daughter just admitted
everything was her doing.
She helped you dispose of the
gas cylinders.
Now you're taking the rap for everything.
If you tell us the truth,
maybe we can help you.
She really has nothing to do with it.
It was me. I planned the whole thing.
My daughter would rather suffer
than be a burden to anyone.
Why would she murder anyone?
She may be paralyzed,
but she has overcome so much.
She finished college
and has a boyfriend who sticks with her.
(A week before the incident)
I thought the worst was over.
Then Ngai Ka-yan showed up
and pushed her further down the abyss.
Sin, what's wrong? Are you hurt?
Don't help me. I can get up.
Come on, let me help you, OK?
I don't need any help.
I don't want to be anyone's burden.
I have been a drag to you and Ching
for too long.
Dad left because I was a burden.
No. I never considered you a burden.
You have a steady job.
You can support yourself and help others.
You're quite brilliant.
But what's the use?
See? I need this wheelchair to get around.
I had to haul the dialysis machine
everywhere I go.
Tell me, what's the point?
Sin, why are you so upset?
Did something happen?
If you're not feeling well,
shall I take you to the doctor?
Why bother? No more doctors.
The world is so unfair.
You and I work so hard,
while Ngai Ka-yan hurt so many people
but he's doing better and better.
Ngai Ka-yan? Jarvis, my Boss?
I didn't paralyze myself in an accident.
Ngai Ka-yan pulled a prank on me.
He paralyzed me.
How did that happen?
How come?
What did he do?
I missed kicking the football and
landed on my back.
Ngai Ka-yan pulled it away
with a fishing line.
He paralyzed me.
I can't believe I worked for him
for a few years,
and he was the one who paralyzed
my daughter.
Ngai Ka-yan, you scumbag!
Auntie Ching, just put them down.
I want to tell you the answer is no.
I simply enjoy the pleasure of
pulling a prank on someone.
I wanted to slap him so bad.
But I know it won't do any good.
He enjoys pulling pranks on others,
he's bound to hurt Tom or someone else
during the livestreaming.
I didn't know what to do.
What's this? It stinks!
Then I stumbled upon something...
Those two clowns were up to no good!
No wonder when Wendy picked up
the cylinder, they overreacted.
What are you doing? Don't touch it.
I'm trying to see if it works.
That's the oxygen for the
Static Apnea Challenge.
Can you keep things tidy?
It's a whole box of stink bombs.
You want to embarrass me
in front of the camera?
Where are those two losers?
Wait...if I expose them now,
I'd be letting them off the hook.
If they want to play games, I'm in.
He never questioned why Tom and Paul
wanted to teach him a lesson.
All he cared about was tricking others.
People like him won't cry until
he sees his own coffin.
But I couldn't think of a solution.
Then I found something at the university...
Is it OK to leave this lying around?
Then we'll take it with us for our smoke.
Are you crazy?
This is highly concentrated H2S,
a spark of fire will cause an explosion.
Don't exaggerate.
Have you heard of swamp gas?
It's about the same.
A whiff can kill you...
When I overheard their conversation,
the first thing that came to mind
I was working part-time, filling in
for someone else.
No one would know I stole the cylinder.
(Biohazard)
Oh dear, I forgot to clean Tim's office.
How forgetful of me!
Don't wait for me. You go ahead.
I'll go back and clean up.
I had a false sense of security,
thinking it was Heaven's will
to help me avenge Sin.
When I was stealing the cylinders,
I noticed they have different
colors and labels.
I didn't know which was which,
so I took one from each box
and will look them up later at home.
Hydrogen sulfide.
So these are not what I want.
Come in!
Mom, why did you hide in your room
right after dinner?
You're not feeling well?
No, I'm counting my money.
What's up? You want to share
your secret with me?
I've been thinking...
I have decided to declare war
on Ngai Ka-yan.
Good!
After what the scumbag did to you,
I won't let him off easy.
Tell me, how do you want your revenge?
I don't want revenge.
But you said you want to declare war.
I think...if he knew something
he did for fun,
put me in a wheelchair,
he might feel guilty and regret it.
I intend to meet with him,
stop him from hurting people again
by stopping his pranks.
Good!
You should give him a chance.
Right there, I dropped the idea
of killing him.
I don't know if that scumbag would
listen to Hiu-sin,
so I followed her to the school.
Sure enough, he was a genuine scumbag.
If you were destined to be paralyzed,
you still couldn't have dodged it.
I'm not talking to a lunatic
Yes!
You're crazy!
People get hurt in accidents every day.
Should we just stay home and do nothing?
How I wanted to stab and kill him
right then and there.
But I told myself I must be patient.
Morning, Auntie Ching...
Because I can kill the scumbag without
anyone knowing about it.
That day, I arrived at the channel
at 12 o'clock.
Though I prepared the poison gas,
I didn't know if Jarvis has swapped
the cylinder.
So I couldn't do anything.
Morning, everyone!
Morning!
That scumbag came in soon afterwards
and greeted me in a happy mood.
After he went inside his office,
I saw him take out a gas cylinder
from his backpack.
That must be the oxygen he planned to
use on Tom and Paul.
He left soon afterwards.
I heard he was meeting Daisy for lunch.
He didn't take his backpack or
lock his office.
I knew they were livestreaming
the Challenge after lunch.
That was my only chance.
But Paul and Wendy started their livecast
then and there.
I went back to the pantry
and waited for them to finish so I could
get into the office.
As you can see...we have shredded paper.
I'm not lying.
But their show went on and on...
I hope you'll like today's magic.
Remember to CLS. See you next time...
When they finally finished,
I knew that was the best chance.
I saw Wendy take out the garbage.
Tom went into the conference room.
I went in to swap the cylinders.
At that moment, it dawned on me,
after I left, this door will be
Jarvis' gate of Hell
and I'll become a murderer.
I hesitated. Do I really want to do this?
Even if you can't catch me,
I won't have peace of mind
for the rest of my life,
or keep my head up in front of my daughter.
Auntie Ching, something is broken.
Can you clean that up?
I was so scared.
I was holding onto the cylinder,
Paul wanted me to clean up something.
I didn't want him to see me
holding the cylinder.
So I stuck it behind the model
and will try to get it back later.
But the paint I got on my hand
can prove I was in the room,
so I washed it off right away
in the toilet.
I didn't see anyone when I came out.
I wanted to get back into Jarvis' office
right away to get the cylinder.
But Tom suddenly came out
from the men's room.
Auntie Ching, I'll help you dump
this in the back stairs.
Don't cut yourself.
Tom, what are you doing here?
You have nothing better to do?
Get back in...
Jarvis came back at that time.
Paul, have you packed up everything?
It's almost 2 o'clock.
Then he went back to his office.
All set and ready to go.
Go down for the set up. I'll be down later.
Then I saw Daisy go into Jarvis' office.
Soon afterwards, they left
with the backpack.
Right then, I knew I'm in trouble.
Only he has the key to the room.
I couldn't go in to get the poison gas.
After the accident, we went to the channel
to look for evidence.
You were the only one there.
Were you trying to retrieve the cylinder?
Yes. I tried looking for the spare key.
I couldn't get in and get the cylinder.
When I heard Jarvis died from
inhaling poison gas,
my heart almost skipped a beat.
I kept wondering if I was involved.
I swapped the cylinders back.
Did Jarvis pick up the wrong one?
Or did I mix them up?
I wanted to know whether the one
behind the model was still there.
I wasn't sure if you would find it.
In the end, I didn't see it
and you locked the door after you.
When you started to suspect Tom and Paul,
I consoled myself
maybe Tom screwed up
when he prepared the cylinders.
But I still felt uneasy.
That's why you quit?
Daisy later told me,
she got the cylinder from Jarvis' backpack.
I lost the last excuse I gave myself.
I must have gotten them mixed up
and Jarvis died from inhaling my cylinder.
Why did you quit your university job?
I know you'll find the source of
the poison gas sooner or later.
I was just trying to buy time.
I was hoping to go away with Sin.
I just didn't expect Wendy to suspect me.
Wendy?
She got ahold of the video of
Sin and Jarvis at the playground.
She figured out I wanted to kill Jarvis.
I deleted the video
and headed out to the airport.
I really thought I could get away.
Were you wearing this pin on the
day in question?
I don't like accessories.
I have never seen it.
I told you everything.
Will my daughter be OK?
We'll check out your story
before we know if your daughter is involved.
Get in!
Mom!
Sin...
Let go...
Madam, please put me in this cell.
She's my daughter. She has kidney problems.
Let me watch over her.
If anything should happen,
I can get help right away.
Please, Madam?
Over there! Come with me.
Sin!
Thank you, Madam! Thanks...
Mom!
Why didn't you listen to me?
Why didn't you get on the plane?
I can't bear to see you spend
the rest of your life in here.
Why didn't you get on the plane?
I can't bear to see you spend
the rest of your life in here.
The officer said even if you
didn't kill anyone,
you tried to dispose of the cylinders.
They're likely to charge you with
obstruction of justice.
How could I be so careless
and let you find those cylinders?
Because you made me move back home.
When I saw the box full of hydrogen sulfide,
I knew you were connected to Jarvis' death.
The whole box?
I checked the words online.
Only the cylinder I took was
hydrogen sulfide.
Hydrogen sulfide is the name in English.
Its molecular formula is H2S.
It's highly concentrated.
I was planning to return them
to the university.
I thought they won't notice
one were missing.
I meant to dispose of them for you.
When I found them missing,
I thought you got rid of them already.
But you just put it on the shelf
and Mrs. Chan almost found them.
Since I found out your secret,
I haven't been able to sleep.
I was worried when I open my eyes
the next day,
you would have been arrested by the Police.
This is why you didn't tell me
your kidney deteriorated
and tried to go places with me.
You told me there's a new treatment
and it's free.
You only wanted me to leave town.
I should have planned it better.
If I chased Switzerland harder,
I really could have taken you away.
Let it be. Even if we got away,
I must still live with a guilty conscience.
Mom, that scumbag is not worth it.
You can't bear to see me suffer.
How can I bear to see that scumbag
bully you?
Actually...I wasn't thinking straight.
I never intended to give up.
Whatever that scumbag did to me,
I will persist.
We still have so much to do together.
That's part of my experience in life.
I will bear the consequences of my action.
(Three months after the incident)
The defendant of livestreaming murder
will be arraigned tomorrow.
We didn't have enough to nail her.
Luckily Gogo Sir had the nerve
to set a bait.
What's on your mind? Auntie Ching
goes to court tomorrow.
She admitted to everything,
except dropping the pin.
Gogo Sir, are you kidding me?
You're still thinking about that
after three months?
No wonder you seldom have tea
with us lately.
Over-exertion won't help you think.
Hurry up and finish your sandwich.
Wait...shouldn't there be two pieces?
How come there's only one left?
You're not concentrating,
you had no idea what you ate.
I only heard you talk about
who swapped the cylinders.
I got so bored listening to that.
Can't you talk about something else?
There's something I want to ask you.
Did you think of something?
Didn't you say someone broke a vase?
Yes!
Was it expensive?
And I thought you had a new angle.
What a shame if someone broke
an antique vase.
It must be expensive.
How come whoever broke it
didn't have to pay for it?
That's odd.
Besides, breaking a vase was so loud,
how come nobody heard the bang?
You're right! How come nobody
heard the noise?
I heard the door open and close.
Someone must have come in and went out.
When the vase was broken,
Auntie Ching should be inside
Ngai Ka-yan's office.
Auntie Ching was worried the paint
could prove she was in the room,
so she went to the toilet to wash her hands.
After you threw out the garbage,
did you go straight to the toilet?
Or did you go somewhere else?
Because I had makeup in my bag,
I went straight to the toilet.
Did you hear any weird noises outside?
No.
Daisy said one person went into the toilet,
but both Auntie Ching and Wendy
claimed they were in there.
Wendy, you're lying.
You couldn't have been to the toilet.
Where were you at the time?
Did you break the vase and kill Ngai Ka-yan?
Based on your analysis,
Wendy is the real killer?
I can't be sure.
We can't rule out the possibility of
her lying for other reasons.
Before we find other leads,
everything is just talk.
If we still have doubts,
why are we still charging Auntie Ching?
Because she admitted everything.
Circumstantial evidence is against her.
I still think the case has too many
questionable points.
(Brand new prankster channel)
(A channel tailor made for Hong Kongers)
What's this? It stinks.
(Brand new program)
Arrest me...
Bust me, officer...
(Brand new cast)
(Brand new name)
(Stay tuned for IOY Channel)
These three videos were shot by Agent J.
Is this a new logo?
You said Lok Hiu-sin told you
these alphabets stand for
a high school group called
Youth Investment Organization.
Why did it become IOY?
IOY Channel will livestream in ten minutes.
Those who want to watch,
use the toilet now and grab your popcorn.
See you later.
Let's go check it out.
Right!
By following their livestreaming,
they should be somewhere around here.
Wake up...
Get him...
He can't get up...
Stop it! You think this is fun?
That's what we like, butt out!
You swallowed dynamite
or having your period?
Maybe it stopped...
Looks like Auntie is still using
social media for the elderly.
Do you know about Reels?
Don't lecture us if you don't, old hag.
You won't understand now.
In a few years, you'll know how
childish this is.
Yes, that's why we want to have fun now.
That's being young.
Why don't you join us?
Maybe you'll rejuvenate and can walk again.
I'm not interested, I only want to know
who told you to imitate Ngai Ka-yan
and make these videos.
Why should I tell you?
Police!
Let's split...
Bye, bye, officers!
Miss Lok, you're out on bail,
don't be reckless.
You're here because you saw the new logo.
I told you it's YIO and not IOY.
Whoever orchestrated this
is likely to be connected to
Ngai Ka-yan's death.
Never mind that now.
You know your mother is worried about you.
Let's find the real killer together.
In the past few months, I drilled my Mom
about the details of the swap.
She couldn't have done it.
She didn't kill Ngai Ka-yan.
Gogo Sir, I found something.
I remember the trick these kids pulled.
Ngai Ka-yan did it before.
It was a trending topic.
I checked the three videos they posted.
They were all trending videos
by Ngai Ka-yan.
Neighbor Vs Stink Bomb, 385,000 views.
Live from Sorry Sir, 420,000 views.
Pigswill Life A or B, 455,000 views.
Tangled Shoelaces, 480,000 views.
That many?
They put Ngai Ka-yan's videos
on a ranking list.
That means, if we follow the
most popular video,
we'll be able to find those kids.
Yes, but the problem is,
the video with the highest viewership
is the Static Apnea Challenge.
They want to do another death on livestream?